翻译:neko，校对:neko，字幕:东云kukono 请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责
Come in
请进
Hey bro, what's happenin'?
嘿，老哥，啥事儿啊？
Hey, come on in. Close the door.
进来，把门关好
sure
没问题
Bo! What the hell are you doing here?
bo，你丫又到这里来想搞什么飞机啊？
I told you last time you came by the station drunk as all hell - not to come by!
你特么上次来这里发酒疯时
我已经跟你说过让你丫不许再来了
Hey can I come by to my big bro once in a while? God,I mean... I'm not drunk now, smoked a few
难道俺就不能来看看俺兄弟了？
哦，俺是说，俺现在没醉，只不过抽了点烟
But just came by to say hey
俺只是来问个好的
So let me guess what the problem is this time - dinero
那让老子猜猜你丫这次又来麻烦老子什么事了-关于钱么
So what?
那又怎样？
It's a loan! (Choro~n!) Come on, I'm good for it.You know me, I got a job doing a...
其实和一项贷款有关，放心我这次有把握
大哥你知道我刚找到了一份工作，是关于...
You know what bro? Just kill that right now because you know what
你丫知道不？不要给老子玩这种老把戏了
you're always getting these bull shit job sthat never materialize,ok?
你特么总是搞上一些根本挣不到钱的s13工作，不是吗？
And you need to get that crap off your arms, those cartoon figures, they're not cutting it.
你丫要找工作，先给老子把胳膊上的那s13纹身给抹了
I can get you a job at the cadet program, be fighting fires, you'll love it.
其实老子到是有份工作给你，就是在老子的消防署
你应该会喜欢
I love fire... I love fire ... I, I , I just, I, it fascinates me! I, I can't help it.
我就是喜欢火啊，我真的喜欢火..
不不不，俺只是说俺对火着迷
俺看见火就忍不住。你知道的，火的颜色就让俺兴奋
It's like...the colours, you know ... I uh...it turns me on .. he he, it does,
你知道的，火的颜色就让俺兴奋
I don't know why but it does.
俺也不知道是什么原因但俺就是觉得爽
Listen man, I gotta lay something on ya I wanna talk to you...
好了，老子还有些事情想和你丫说说
Something thats been bothering me
一些最近让老子非常不爽的事情
Here we go, another big brother lecture again
好啊好啊，大哥又要搞思想品德讲座是吧？
Watch where you're going, fag boy!
你丫s13！走路长眼睛了吗？
Why don't you get f@cked?
你丫欠*吧？
Cause everyone in the station already had a piece of your ass.
其实你丫菊花已经被我们*遍了
HEY,HEY,HEY Cameron! The chief is right there.
嘿嘿嘿，池田，老大（比利王）就在附近呢！
C'mon honey you want me to f@ck you in the ass?C'mon c'mon
宝贝（池田）别跟这s13一般见识
不如咱俩再去深♂入交流一下吧？
And you! you better watch yourself dude, because you're f@cking playing with fire with me!
还有你丫（指藤冈），你特么最好跟老子注意点
你丫再跟老子叫板老子灭了你
Let's go.
闪人！
bob，well what im trying to say is
bob，我想说的是
ro, its, um its me
兄弟，就是，额就是我
I wanna talk to you about me, bro
我想跟你谈谈关于我自己的一些事情
you?
你?
Whats wrong big brother?
有啥事呢大兄弟?
You can talk, what's wrong
你说说看，发生了啥
um, you remember the time we were hanging out
那么，记得那次我们一起出去的时候吗
we got drunk, and I started talking to you about,(蜜汁停顿), about those feelings
那次我喝醉了，然后开始告诉你关于我的那些
关于那些感♂觉
what, the gay stuff?
啥？那种GAY的感觉吗
well, to tell you the truth, its these fantasies I'm talking about
说实话，我的这种感♂觉是越来越严重了
um, I'm having more and more, and uh
而且这种感觉越来越强烈
they are really turning me on
已经让我有点不能自持了
uh, like the other day when I was in the shower
例如上次我在淋浴时（定冈篇...）
and uh, I was fantasizing about everybody else in the shower
我对周围和我一起淋浴的男人身体都发生了兴趣
we were all beating off together
我们一起做了点事情
and um, I like it.
然后，我喜欢这样
you know, the other night, one of the boys were sleeping
然后那天我们组的一个小子睡觉时
and I am reach that place with dick♂
我用我的金金去和他接触了
Sex is sex, guys, girls, doesnt matter，its good~its natural
性爱嘛，男孩，女孩，没什么要紧的，那很好，很自然啊
don't worry about it, its okay~
别担心，这没问题
listen, nobody, nobody knows 'bout this, you understand?
听好了，没有人，没有人可以知道这件事，所以你明白吗？
so keep your f@cking mouth shut, i, serious
你要给我闭上你的臭嘴，我是认真的
come in
进来
Hey chief, sorry to bother you and your company but we've got a scheduling problem
老大好，抱歉打扰你们俩了
但我有个关于计划部署上的问题
we need to talk about now.
需要和你谈谈
Steve, this is my little brother - Bo. He was just leaving.
藤冈，这是俺弟，他马上就走的
I was? Pleasure to meet you
我没这样说吧...很高兴认识你
Sorry, I'll come back in a bit.
那抱歉，我等下再来
No no no, no big problem just give me 15 minutes.
不用不用，没啥大事，你等十五分钟就行
Now there's an ass I wouldn't mind f@cking, you know what I mean.
哇，这朵菊花不错值得一采(现在有只屁股我不介意操)
哥你懂的
Well, that's the new cadet. He's gay,
好吧，这是我们的新人
and he's been catching a lot of flak around the station from all the other guys too about it
他很这里的很多兄贵交流♂过
because he is cool, and he's out of the closet
还是个出柜了的基佬，因此颇受关注
Hey big bro, you and I should take him up on the roof and show him twenty inches of pleasure,
我说哥啊，咱俩其实应该将他带到房顶上
并让他享受一下20英寸的快乐
you know what I'm saying, hm?
你知道我意思吧，嗯?
Yeah, right. You know what?
我c，你特么在说啥啊？
You keep your f@cking grubby hands off of him, and get out,
你tm给老子听好了，离他远点，并且现在就给我滚出去！
and make sure you leave through the back
而且给我从后门滚
Shut your f@cking mouth!
你丫跟老子闭嘴吧！
We share the same blood! Don't pull this f@cking high and mighty shit with me,
亏得你丫还是老子的亲哥哥
不要整天给在老子面前得瑟些表面文章
You've been this way ever since you became a fireman. Mr big shot fire chief,
你丫不就是当了个消防员吗？
好了，我的超人署长哥，你不喜欢失火
you hate it when things burn. Always trying to save the world,
总是整天想着拯救地球之类的大事
well save the world bro, save the world.
好吧你就去当你的超人拯救世界吧
ou know what dude? You just dialed the wrong number.Ok?
你特么s13，你特么真的把老子给惹火了
You wanna f@ck with me? You're a f@cking psycho, ok?
好吧，你丫和老子叫板，老子看是你是脑子烧坏了
Get of the dope, get of the booze, and I dont give a f@ck what you do
好吧你丫爱咋样咋样吧，抽你丫的大烟去吧
喝你丫的猫尿去吧，老子再也不管你了
but for now, get the f@ck out
但现在，老子命令你立刻给我滚出去！( '-' )ノ)`-' )
f@ck you.f@ck you, ptsss, you f@cking shit big brother
f@ck youヽ(‘⌒´メ)ノ，切，该死的大哥
Hey chief
嘿，老大
hey whats up bro?
嘿，兄弟怎么了？
I just saw your brother... in the back of the station with one of our jackets on, and ... well.
你弟刚才...刚才穿了我们消防署的制服从后门出去了...
he wasn't wearing any pants.
而且...而且他没穿裤子
Son of a bitch.
(｀_ゝ´)
Yo, what's this?  stupid breeder
哟，这是谁啊? 愚蠢的异性恋
Hey chief,（老大！）
Hey whats up?（咋了？）
Well the arson department faxed over our match on the partial finger prints found
刚才有相关部门发传真给我们
那里面有提到在纵火现场发现的指纹，
Has any DNA come up on that white slimy stuff?
和现场的白色黏液的DNA鉴定结果的匹配关系了吗？
No do me a favor though, take the fax, put it on my desk and
还没，帮我把传真放在我的桌子上吧
lock it in my office and Imma go upstairs work out some bad tension
并且锁在我的办公室里，我要去楼上放松一下了
I need to be alone for a bit.
我需要单独待一会
Sure chief, I'll let everyone know to stay clear of the roof
（没问题，我会要其他人不去楼顶打扰您的）
Thanks alot
（谢了！）
ok
（没啥）